Abdulaziz Albadawi

Full Stack Designer

Abdulaziz Hamad Albadawi

Cairo, Egypt

(+20) 127 121 8832 albadawiabdulaziz@gmail.com

Skills

I have experience with more than 3 years in UI/UX with classes and courses from Adobe and Udemy, however, now I'm experienced enough to teach other young creative designers with the latest teaching methods using the latest technologies, I have mastered Adobe Illustrator and Photoshop, Figma, Adobe XD, InVision and Adobe InDesign.

Experience

Quak ~ Co-Founder/ Chief Design Officer

October 2018- PRESENT, Cairo, Egypt

I led the research, prototyping, usability testing, and design the new version Beta 1.0.0.

I also helped design the MVP Quak.

Freelancer / Full stack designer

January 2017 - October 2018, Giza, Egypt

I designed logos, websites, posters, user interfaces and various social media content for multiple clients. The majority of this work was completed remotely.

Rubium studio / UI/UX

July 2019- PRESENT, Cario, Egypt

I contact with the client and deal with them and do the research, wireframing, creating the website interfaces then i test it with the art director

Education

El- Neel School/ Computer Science

October 2014- EXPECT OCTOBER2019, Cairo, Egypt

Studied Computer Science, I chose Data analysis career and got the first place in my school, I learnt powerful software like Python, SQL, Spreadsheet, Machine Learning etc.

Awards

Best learner and most productive learner for 5 weeks in row ~ DataCamp The perfect student Award ~ Regional Government Best speech ~ Cairo International model United Nation 1st place for my research how to achieve goal ~ El-Neel School